<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="applicationName">Backup My Apps</string>
    <string name="textViewApplicationInformation">This application is designed for doing a backup of your installed packages / applications on your device. It stores just meta information of the packages to bunch-install them through the market on another device or after a factory reset of your device.</string>
    <string name="buttonBackupInstalledApplications">Backup application list</string>
    <string name="buttonRestoreInstalledApplications">Restore (install) applications</string>
    <string name="textViewCurrentProcess">No current progress</string>
    <string name="dialogMessageNoExternalStorageMounted">It seems that there is no external storage device mounted on your device. This application relies on having such a device and will close now.</string>
    <string name="buttonOk">OK</string>
    <string name="progressDialogBackupInProgress">Gathering and saving application backup information. Please wait...</string>
    <string name="dialogMessageNotImplemented">Unfortunately, this feature is currently not implemented. It will be available as soon as possible through an update in the Android Market.</string>
    <string name="menuHelp">Help</string>
    <string name="menuExit">Exit</string>
    <string name="textViewAdditionalInformation">To backup the installed application, press the backup button. The file with the backup information will be stored in %s. To restore the applications place the file with the backup information in the same folder and press the restore button.\n\nFor more information open the menu and select the Help item.</string>
    <string name="dialogTitleHelpDialog">Help</string>
    <string name="buttonCloseHelp">Close help</string>
    <string name="textViewHelpText">This application reads information about the installed applications and stores this information in a XML file. This file can be used to reinstall all applications on a new device or after a factory reset.\n\n As this application is still on heavy development, please expect frequent updates and bus inside of the application.</string>
    <string name="menuAbout">About...</string>
    <string name="dialogTitleAboutDialog">About...</string>
</resources>
