<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="applicationName">Backup My Apps</string>
    <string name="applicationBackupServiceName">Backup My Apps Background Backup Service</string>
    <string name="textViewApplicationInformation">This application is designed for doing a backup of your installed packages / applications on your device. It only stores the meta information of the packages in order to bunch-install them through the market on another device or after a factory reset of your device.</string>
    <string name="buttonBackupInstalledApplications">Backup application list</string>
    <string name="buttonRestoreInstalledApplications">Restore (install) applications</string>
    <string name="dialogMessageNoExternalStorageMounted">It seems that there is no external storage device mounted on your device. This application relies on having such a device and will close now.</string>
    <string name="buttonOk">OK</string>
    <string name="progressDialogBackupInProgress">Gathering and saving application backup information. Please wait...</string>
    <string name="menuHelp">Help</string>
    <string name="dialogTitleHelpDialog">Help</string>
    <string name="textViewHelpText">This application reads information about the installed applications and stores this information in a XML file. This file can be used to reinstall all applications on a new device or after a factory reset.\n\n As this application is still under development, please expect frequent updates and bugs inside the application.</string>
    <string name="dialogTitleAboutDialog">About...</string>
    <string name="textViewAboutAppName">Backup My Apps %s</string>
    <string name="textViewAboutCopyright">Developed 2011 by Tim Hütz</string>
    <string name="textViewAboutArtworkLabel">Artwork</string>
    <string name="textViewAboutArtworkContent">Tango harm-on-icons</string>
    <string name="textViewAboutTranslationsLabel">Translations</string>
    <string name="textViewAboutTranslationsContent">Tim Hütz\nMichaela Gaens</string>
    <string name="progressDialogRestoreInProgress">Restore in progress. Please wait...</string>
    <string name="textViewSelectApplicationToRestore">To restore an application from your backup, click on the application name. The corresponding item will open in the Android Market allowing you to install the application.</string>
    <string name="dialogMessageBackupFailed">Failed to create a list of the installed applications. Please reboot your device and try again.</string>
    <string name="dialogMessageBackupSucceeded">Successfully created the list of the installed applications.</string>
    <string name="menuSettings">Preferences</string>
    <string name="preferenceCategoryBackgroundService">Background service</string>
    <string name="preferenceTitleUseBackupBackgroundService">Use backup background service</string>
    <string name="preferenceSummaryBackgroundServiceOn">The background service will regularly backup your installed applications.</string>
    <string name="preferenceSummaryBackgroundServiceOff">The background service will NOT backup your installed applications.</string>
    <string name="preferenceCategoryBuildVersion">Build-Version</string>
    <string name="preferenceTitleBuildVersion">Build-Version</string>
    <string name="preferenceSummaryBuildVersion">Version: %s</string>
    <string name="preferenceCategorySynchronization">Synchronization</string>
    <string name="preferenceTitleEnableDropboxSynchronization">Use synchronization</string>
    <string name="preferenceSummaryEnableDropboxSynchronizationOn">Data will be stored locally and in your Dropbox account.</string>
    <string name="preferenceSummaryEnableDropboxSynchronizationOff">There will be NO synchronization with Dropbox. Data will only be stored locally.</string>
    <string name="textViewWhatsNewLabel">What\'s new?</string>
    <string name="buttonClose">Close</string>
    <string name="textViewSelectFileToRestore">Please select the backup file you want to restore from on your current device.</string>
    <string name="listItemLocalBackupFile">Local backup file</string>
    <string name="textViewAdditionalInformation">To backup the installed applications, press the backup button. The file with the backup information will be stored in %s. To restore the applications place the file with the backup information in the same folder and press the restore button. Optionally, if you enabled the synchronization option of this application, the restore function will also display backup files found in your Dropbox folder.\n\nFor more information open the menu and select the Help item.</string>
    <string name="progressDialogUploadingToDropbox">Uploading the backup file into your Dropbox folder. Please wait...</string>
    <string name="progressDialogDownloadingFromDropbox">Downloading the backup file from your Dropbox folder. Please wait...</string>
    <string name="menuFeedback">Feedback</string>
    <string name="intentSendFeedback">Send feedback</string>
    <string name="intentSendFeedbackBodyText">Please tell us your opinion about Backup My Apps or even request features you would like to see.</string>
    <string name="preferenceCategoryStatistics">Statistics</string>
    <string name="preferenceTitleUsageStatistics">Send usage statistics</string>
    <string name="preferenceSummaryUsageStatisticsOn">Send anonymous usage statistics to the developer to improve the application.</string>
    <string name="preferenceSummaryUsageStatisticsOff">Do not send any anonymous usage statistics to the developer.</string>
    <string name="dialogTitleRateApp">Please rate the application</string>
    <string name="dialogMessageRateApp">Thank you for using this application. It would be nice if you rate this application in the Android Market. Do you have 10 seconds to do this right now?</string>
    <string name="dialogButtonRateAppYes">Yes</string>
    <string name="dialogButtonRateAppLater">Later</string>
    <string name="dialogButtonRateAppNever">Never</string>
    <string name="textViewWhatsNewText">Thank you for using / updating Backup My Apps. Here are the changes since the last update:\n\n* Application icons are displayed in the restore list\n* Optimized the Dropbox synchronization\n* The Dropbox synchronization can now be enabled properly\n* Several bugfixes</string>
    
    <string name="dialogTitleAllowUsageStatistics">Enable usage statistics</string>
    <string name="dialogMessageAllowUsageStatistics">For optimizing the application we're recording how you use the application (button clicks, time in the different application states and usage time). These information are send anonymously to our server. It would help us really much if you enable this option but if you don't like doing this you can disable acquiring those information. Do you want to enable acquiring and sending anonymous usage statistics?</string>
    <string name="dialogButtonAllowUsageStatistics">Yes</string>
    <string name="dialogButtonDontAllowUsageStatistics">No</string>
</resources>
